<idea-plugin version="2">
  <id>io.edgeg.gtm.intellij</id>
  <name>Git Time Metric</name>
  <version>1.0.4</version>
  <vendor email="gtm@edgeg.io" url="https://github.com/git-time-metric/gtm-jetbrains-plugin">Git Time Metric</vendor>

  <description><![CDATA[
<img src="https://avatars2.githubusercontent.com/u/19735693?v=3&s=200" alt="" height="100" width="100">
<b>Simple, seamless, lightweight time tracking for all your git projects</b><br /><br />

<b>Git Time Metrics (GTM)</b> is a tool to automatically track time spent reading and working on code that you store in a Git repository.<br />
By installing GTM and using supported plug-ins for your favorite editors, you can immediately realize better insight into how you are spending your time and on what files.<br /><br />

<b>Installation</b><br /><br />

Installing GTM is a two step process.  First, it's recommended you install the GTM executable that the plug-in integrates with and then install the JetBrains GTM plug-in. Please submit an issue if you have any problems and/or questions. <br /><br />

1. Follow the <a href=https://github.com/git-time-metric/gtm/blob/master/README.md>Getting Started</a> section to install the GTM executable for your operating system.<br /><br />

2. Install the plug-in from your JetBrains IDE, select Preferences -> Plugins -> Browse Repositories... and search for "Git Time Metric".<br /><br />


<b>Note</b> - to enable time tracking for a Git repository, you need to initialize it with <b>gtm init</b> otherwise it will be ignored by GTM. This is done via the command line. You can run this within the JetBrains IDE terminal.<br /><br />

<code>
> cd /path/to/your/project<br />
> gtm init</code>
<br /><br />

To report a bug, please submit an issue on the <a href=https://github.com/git-time-metric/gtm-jetbrains-plugin/issues>GitHub Page</a>.<br />

Consult the <a href=https://github.com/git-time-metric/gtm/blob/master/README.md>README</a> and <a href=https://github.com/git-time-metric/gtm/wiki>Wiki</a> for more information.

    ]]></description>

  <change-notes><![CDATA[
1.0.4 - 8/8/2016<br />
-----------------------<br />
Require GTM v1.0.0<br />
<br />
1.0.2 - 7/21/2016<br />
------------------------<br />
- Fix path for finding gtm executable on Windows<br />
<br />
<br />
    ]]>
  </change-notes>

  <idea-version since-build="139"/>

  <depends>com.intellij.modules.lang</depends>

  <application-components>
    <component>
      <implementation-class>io.edgeg.gtm.intellij.GitTimeMetric</implementation-class>
    </component>
  </application-components>

  <project-components>
    <component>
      <implementation-class>io.edgeg.gtm.intellij.GTMProject</implementation-class>
    </component>
  </project-components>

</idea-plugin>
